[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chauvet Cave and Meyrieres Cave are two caves located in this European state.", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Netherlands", "Spain", "Belgium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is NOT true about the Common Raven, a popular omnivorous bird?", "correct_answer": "It wouldnt eat birds", "incorrect_answers": ["It wouldnt reject carrion", "It would feed on animal feces", "It feeds on human food waste"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the man Tyler Durden assaults behind the liquor store in the film Fight Club?", "correct_answer": "Raymond K. Hessel", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert J. Stephenson", "Andrew K. Walker", "Jesse L. Martin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What astronomer was the first to see canali on the surface of Mars?", "correct_answer": "Giovanni Shiaparelli", "incorrect_answers": ["Sir Isaac Newton", "Galileo", "Percival Lowell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the nickname of Dustin Hoffmans character in the 1976 thriller movie Marathon Man?", "correct_answer": "Babe", "incorrect_answers": ["Flash", "Sugar", "Twister"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the year of the coin Chigurh tosses with the proprietor of the gas station in No Country for Old Men?", "correct_answer": "1958", "incorrect_answers": ["1968", "1956", "1966"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Geologically, we are in the Quaternary Period of the Cenozoic Era. In which geological epoch are we?", "correct_answer": "Holocene", "incorrect_answers": ["Miocene", "Eocene", "Pliocene"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Wedding Crashers, Todd tied down Jeremy to the bed and was trying to attack him when Secretary Cleary came in the room.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you established Trivia TV and wanted a web site in the .tv domain, which of the following would earn some money?", "correct_answer": "Tuvalu", "incorrect_answers": ["BBC", "Taiwan", "CNN"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the beginning of the movie Dog Day Afternoon, there were 3 men involved in the robbery.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest artery in the body?", "correct_answer": "Aorta", "incorrect_answers": ["Carotid artery", "Epicardium", "Pulmonary artery"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "More than 5 million Jews were killed during the Holocaust.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]